Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪No one left to lean on♪
♪لم يبق أحد يمكن الاعتماد عليه♪
♪No way out, no place to run♪
♪لا مخرج، لا مكان للهروب♪
♪Tears held back inside my eyes♪
♪الدموع محصورة في عيني♪
♪I run against the wind and time♪
♪أركض ضد الريح والوقت♪
♪Loved and lost, regrets remain♪
♪ محبوبون وضائعون، والندم يبقى ♪
♪But tears fall down like gentle rain♪
♪ولكن الدموع تسقط مثل المطر اللطيف♪
♪I look up strong, I grow with pride♪
♪أنظر إلى الأعلى بقوة، وأنمو بفخر♪
♪Living life with heart untied♪
♪عيش الحياة بقلب غير مقيد♪
♪Holding tight♪
♪التمسك بقوة♪
♪The burning faith you gave♪
♪الإيمان المتقد الذي أعطيته♪
♪Healing wounds that fate engraved♪
♪شفاء الجروح التي نقشها القدر♪
♪That light inside my restless soul♪
♪هذا النور داخل روحي المضطربة♪
♪One life to live, one final goal♪
♪حياة واحدة للعيش، وهدف نهائي واحد♪
♪I'll love with courage, wild and free♪
♪سأحب بشجاعة، بوحشية وحرية♪
♪Break through the noise, let them hear me♪
♪اخترق الضوضاء، دعهم يسمعونني♪
♪Holding tight♪
♪التمسك بقوة♪
♪The burning faith you gave♪
♪الإيمان المتقد الذي أعطيته♪
♪Healing wounds that fate engraved♪
♪شفاء الجروح التي نقشها القدر♪
♪That light inside my restless soul♪
♪هذا النور داخل روحي المضطربة♪
♪One life to live, one final goal♪
♪حياة واحدة للعيش، وهدف نهائي واحد♪
♪I'll love with courage, wild and free♪
♪سأحب بشجاعة، بوحشية وحرية♪
♪Break through the noise, let them hear me♪
♪اخترق الضوضاء، دعهم يسمعونني♪
=Dragon King's Decree=
=مرسوم ملك التنين=
=Episode 30=
=الحلقة 30=
She is
هي هي
being reborn from the flames
الولادة من جديد من بين النيران
like a phoenix.
مثل طائر الفينيق.
♪Like petals fall, gone with the clouds♪
♪مثل البتلات المتساقطة، ذهبت مع السحب♪
♪Like stars fade fast in open skies♪
♪مثل النجوم تتلاشى بسرعة في السماء المفتوحة♪
This is the the token you gave me
هذا هو الرمز الذي أعطيته لي
on our first day of marriage.
في يومنا الأول من الزواج.
♪Like snowflakes melting softly in the evening haze♪
♪مثل رقاقات الثلج التي تذوب برفق في ضباب المساء♪
Only a true Wujing Saintess
فقط قديسة وو جينغ الحقيقية
can awaken the Fire Phoenix pendant's power of rebirth.
يمكن أن يوقظ قلادة Fire Phoenix قوة إعادة الميلاد.
But you really did die once.
لكنك مت بالفعل مرة واحدة.
It must have hurt.
لا بد أن يكون الأمر مؤلمًا.
But you made it through.
ولكنك نجحت في ذلك.
If you hadn't shown up,
لو لم تظهر،
I thought I'd really lost you.
اعتقدت أنني فقدتك حقًا.
♪Like evening breeze that stirs soft hair in twilight♪
♪مثل نسيم المساء الذي يحرك الشعر الناعم في الشفق♪
♪Like fleeting thoughts that surge and then unwind♪
♪مثل الأفكار العابرة التي تتدفق ثم تتلاشى♪
♪Chance meetings fade, just empty rooms left behind♪
♪تتلاشى اللقاءات العرضية، وتبقى الغرف الفارغة فقط♪
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
It'll all be over soon.
كل شيء سينتهي قريبا.
♪Light as a feather, yet it sank an island deep in me♪
♪خفيفة كالريشة، لكنها غرقت في جزيرة عميقة في داخلي♪
I'm sorry
أنا آسف
for making you worry.
لإزعاجك.
I owe you one.
أنا مدين لك بواحدة.
♪Leaving me lost in memories, small and fading away♪
♪تركني ضائعًا في الذكريات، صغيرة وتتلاشى♪
We should give Prince Zhi
ينبغي لنا أن نعطي الأمير تشي
and that fake Saintess Liluo
وتلك القديسة المزيفة ليلو
our sincerest wedding gift.
هدية زفافنا الصادقة.
I am the Wujing Saintess.
أنا قديس وو جينغ.
I've been that since I was born!
لقد كنت كذلك منذ ولادتي!
Such audacity.
هذه الجرأة.
Guards,
حراس،
get her out of here.
أخرجها من هنا.
I am the real Saintess.
أنا القديسة الحقيقية.
Prince Zhi,
الأمير زهي,
how dare you do this to me?
كيف تجرؤ على فعل هذا بي؟
Let go!
اتركه!
You have to return to the sanctuary and give His Majesty
عليك أن تعود إلى الحرم وتسلم على جلالته
an explanation on this matter.
توضيح بشأن هذه المسألة.
You have an extreme yin constitution
لديك دستور يين متطرف
and improved your War God Constitution with the dragon pearl.
وقم بتحسين دستور إله الحرب الخاص بك باستخدام لؤلؤة التنين.
All signs confirm
كل الدلائل تؤكد ذلك
you are the real Wujing Saintess.
أنت القديسة وو جينغ الحقيقية.
Please come back with us to the sanctuary.
من فضلك عد معنا إلى الحرم.
Now you acknowledge me
الآن أنت تعترف بي
because you're in danger.
لأنك في خطر.
You two should leave.
ينبغي لكما أن تغادرا.
Chu Moshang and I are already married,
أنا وتشو موشانغ متزوجان بالفعل،
but the sanctuary's collapse is still ongoing.
لكن انهيار الحرم لا يزال مستمرا.
Young Master,
السيد الشاب،
we should hurry back to the sanctuary.
ينبغي لنا أن نسارع بالعودة إلى الحرم.
She was right.
لقد كانت على حق.
The Dragon King's Decree prophecy
نبوءة مرسوم ملك التنين
can't save the sanctuary.
لا يمكن انقاذ الحرم.
I'll wait for you here.
سأنتظرك هنا.
Shang,
شانغ،
you were right.
لقد كنت على حق.
Marrying the Wujing Saintess
الزواج من قديسة ووجينج
can't save the sanctuary from this disaster.
لا يمكن إنقاذ الحرم من هذه الكارثة.
We were all wrong.
لقد كنا جميعا مخطئين.
Is this the end of the sanctuary?
هل هذه نهاية الحرم؟
Your Majesty,
جلالتك،
Prince Zhi has always known
الأمير تشي كان يعرف دائما
Liluo isn't the true Wujing Saintess.
ليلو ليست قديسة وو جينغ الحقيقية.
How should he be punished?
كيف يتم معاقبته؟
When a Dragon makes mistakes,
عندما يرتكب التنين أخطاءً،
it's never just simple lectures.
إنها ليست مجرد محاضرات بسيطة.
With the Black and White Envoys here,
مع المبعوثين السود والبيض هنا،
I believe they'll carry out the fairest execution.
أعتقد أنهم سينفذون الإعدام الأكثر عدلاً.
Winner takes all.
الفائز يأخذ كل شيء.
I accept the consequences.
أقبل العواقب.
I have nothing more to say.
ليس لدي المزيد لأقوله.
Prince Zhi angered the Dragon God.
أغضب الأمير تشي إله التنين.
His crime is unforgivable.
جريمته لا تغتفر.
He's sentenced to endless torment,
لقد حُكم عليه بالعذاب الذي لا نهاية له،
repeating forever
يتكرر إلى الأبد
until he earns the Dragon God's forgiveness.
حتى يحصل على مغفرة إله التنين.
Father,
أب،
even till the very last moment,
حتى اللحظة الأخيرة،
you never cared about me.
لم تهتم بي أبدًا.
I'll make sure you regret
سوف أتأكد من أنك ستندم
the decision you made today.
القرار الذي اتخذته اليوم.
Mother.
الأم.
Zhilou.
جيلو.
Wujing Saintess, congratulations
ووجينج سانتيس، تهانينا
for reclaiming everything that belongs to you.
لاستعادة كل ما ينتمي إليك.
But...
لكن...
what if it's all been a mistake?
ماذا لو كان كل هذا خطأ؟
What if I'm not really the Wujing Saintess?
ماذا لو لم أكن حقا قديسة وو جينغ؟
Zhilou,
جيلو،
even if you're not the Wujing Saintess,
حتى لو لم تكوني قديسة وو جينغ،
to us,
لنا،
you'll always be one.
سوف تظل دائما واحدا.
The Wujing Saintess' coronation never requires proof.
تتويج القديسة وو جينغ لا يحتاج إلى دليل أبدًا.
Only the world's acceptance.
فقط قبول العالم.
To me, our Dragon Queen
بالنسبة لي، ملكة التنين لدينا
is incomparable in the world.
لا مثيل لها في العالم.
You're the best.
أنت الأفضل.
Zhilou,
جيلو،
you deserve to be the Wujing Saintess.
أنت تستحق أن تكون قديسة Wujing.
Feng Zhilou!
فنغ تشيلو!
Why did you wear my battle robe?
لماذا ارتديت رداء المعركة الخاص بي؟
You witch.
أنت ساحرة.
I can't kill you no matter how hard I try.
لا أستطيع قتلك مهما حاولت.
I can't escape you no matter where I hide.
لا أستطيع الهروب منك أينما كنت.
And now you even dare to wear my battle robe?
والآن هل تجرؤ على ارتداء رداء المعركة الخاص بي؟
I'm the real Wujing Saintess!
أنا القديسة وو جينغ الحقيقية!
I'm the future Dragon Queen!
أنا ملكة التنين المستقبلية!
It's me!
هذا أنا!
Her blood poisoning is flaring up.
تسمم دمها يتفاقم.
My hair.
شعري.
My face!
وجهي!
Why is this happening?
لماذا يحدث هذا؟
Karma is catching up.
الكارما تلاحقنا.
I don't want this.
انا لا أريد هذا.
I...
أنا...
I don't want to become like my mother.
لا أريد أن أصبح مثل أمي.
No way.
مستحيل.
Mother,
الأم،
please save me.
من فضلك أنقذني.
To become the Dragon Queen,
لتصبح ملكة التنين،
she didn't even get to see her mother one last time.
ولم تتمكن حتى من رؤية والدتها للمرة الأخيرة.
No!
لا!
The sanctuary.
الحرم.
I'm going to the sanctuary.
سأذهب إلى الحرم.
I can't just die like this.
لا أستطيع أن أموت هكذا.
Zhilou,
جيلو،
go on.
إستمر.
Shang,
شانغ،
what are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
He's sacrificing himself.
إنه يضحي بنفسه.
He's transferring his life force to the Tree of Life to protect the sanctuary's barrier.
إنه ينقل قوة حياته إلى شجرة الحياة لحماية حاجز الحرم.
Saving the sanctuary has always been our duty as people
لقد كان إنقاذ الحرم المقدس واجبنا كشعب دائمًا
of the sanctuary.
من الحرم.
His life force isn't enough.
قوة حياته ليست كافية.
We'll do our part too.
وسوف نقوم بدورنا أيضًا.
This is the real power of the Dragon King
هذه هي القوة الحقيقية لملك التنين
and the Wujing Saintess.
و Wujing Saintess.
Yes, it worked.
نعم لقد نجح الأمر.
This is great.
هذا عظيم.
Honey,
عسل،
help me gather these herbs.
ساعدني في جمع هذه الأعشاب.
It's basically a miracle.
إنها معجزة في الأساس.
His lordship actually regained his sight
لقد استعاد سيده بصره بالفعل
and opened the apothecary to us.
وفتح لنا الصيدلية.
My stomach feels a bit off.
أشعر أن معدتي ليست على ما يرام.
That's nothing.
هذا لا شيء.
His lordship's wife is blessed by the Dragon God.
زوجة سيده مباركة من قبل إله التنين.
Even her muteness is cured.
حتى أن خرسهم تم شفاؤه.
Yeah.
نعم.
It's a miracle.
إنها معجزة.
A real miracle.
معجزة حقيقية.
Xiaoyu.
شياويو.
Is this...
هذا هو...
You forgot already?
هل نسيت بالفعل؟
I just told you yesterday.
لقد قلت لك بالأمس فقط.
This is poria.
هذه بوريا.
And this is codonopsis.
وهذا هو الكودونوبسيس.
♪Like petals fall, gone with the clouds♪
♪مثل البتلات المتساقطة، ذهبت مع السحب♪
Come on, get it together.
هيا، اجمعوا شتات أنفسكم.
It's an important occasion.
إنها مناسبة مهمة.
You're worse than Hunbao.
أنت أسوأ من هونباو.
♪Like stars fade fast in open skies♪
♪مثل النجوم تتلاشى بسرعة في السماء المفتوحة♪
Don't compare me to Hunbao.
لا تقارنني بهونباو.
He's just a flood dragon,
إنه مجرد تنين فيضان،
and I'm his superior.
وأنا رئيسه.
I'm going to become
انا سوف اصبح
a flood dragon as mighty as His Majesty.
تنين الطوفان قوي مثل جلالته.
To me, you're just a stupid flood dragon.
بالنسبة لي، أنت مجرد تنين فيضان غبي.
You stupid bird.
أيها الطائر الغبي.
You...
أنت...
Childish.
طفولي.
♪Like fireflies flicker through wild grass, fleeting light♪
♪مثل اليراعات التي تومض عبر العشب البري، ضوء عابر♪
♪Like evening breeze that stirs soft hair in twilight♪
♪مثل نسيم المساء الذي يحرك الشعر الناعم في الشفق♪
Welcome back to the sanctuary, Your Majesties!
مرحباً بكم مجدداً في الحرم الشريف، يا أصحاب الجلالة!
Your Majesties.
يا أصحاب الجلالة.
♪Light as a feather, yet it sank an island deep in me♪
♪خفيفة كالريشة، لكنها غرقت في جزيرة عميقة في داخلي♪
♪In that one moment, life's grip I couldn't break or sway♪
♪في تلك اللحظة، لم أستطع كسر قبضة الحياة أو التخلص منها♪
♪Leaving me lost in memories, small and fading away♪
♪تركني ضائعًا في الذكريات، صغيرة وتتلاشى♪
Greetings, my lord!
مرحباً سيدي!
Greetings, my lord.
تحياتي سيدي.
(With the Tree of Life withering,)
(مع ذبول شجرة الحياة)
(the Demons from the nether realm are invading the mortal realm.)
(الشياطين من عالم السفلي يغزون عالم البشر.)
(What are we waiting for?)
(ماذا ننتظر؟)
♪Like petals fall, gone with the clouds♪
♪مثل البتلات المتساقطة، ذهبت مع السحب♪
♪Like stars fade fast in open skies♪
♪مثل النجوم تتلاشى بسرعة في السماء المفتوحة♪
♪Like snowflakes melting softly in the evening haze♪
♪مثل رقاقات الثلج التي تذوب برفق في ضباب المساء♪
♪Like your fleeting glance that gave me one brief dream's grace♪
♪مثل نظرتك العابرة التي منحتني نعمة حلم قصير♪
♪Like fireflies flicker through wild grass, fleeting light♪
♪مثل اليراعات التي تومض عبر العشب البري، ضوء عابر♪
♪Like evening breeze that stirs soft hair in twilight♪
♪مثل نسيم المساء الذي يحرك الشعر الناعم في الشفق♪
♪Like fleeting thoughts that surge and then unwind♪
♪مثل الأفكار العابرة التي تتدفق ثم تتلاشى♪
♪Chance meetings fade, just empty rooms left behind♪
♪تتلاشى اللقاءات العرضية، وتبقى الغرف الفارغة فقط♪
♪You brought a wave that stirred a wild, restless sea♪
♪لقد جلبت موجة أثارت بحرًا هائجًا لا يهدأ♪
♪Light as a feather, yet it sank an island deep in me♪
♪خفيفة كالريشة، لكنها غرقت في جزيرة عميقة في داخلي♪
♪In that one moment, life's grip I couldn't break or sway♪
♪في تلك اللحظة، لم أستطع كسر قبضة الحياة أو التخلص منها♪
♪Leaving me lost in memories, small and fading away♪
♪تركني ضائعًا في الذكريات، صغيرة وتتلاشى♪